You
I'm growing tired of it, so I'm putting an end to you now
Hinokami Kagura
Raging Sun
Flame dance that was underwhelming but
He's gone?
Hinokami Kagura! Fake Rainbow!
I can do this!
Hinokami Kagura! Firewheel!
Firewheel!
Quickly! Recovery! Breathing!
I can do this! I can take on an upper rank demon!
I can do this. I can take on an upper-ranked demon!
I can take on an upper-ranked demon.
No. It's more like the ones that were split off are now returning to her.
Stand your ground. Get your breathing under control.
And strike!
I knew it.
She's gone!
It seems I was right.
Hashira really did show up!
How magnificent!
I can't even imagine how pleased my master will be!
She just transformed.
Her scent couldn't be more ominous.
It's making me sick already.
Which means she gained even more power.
But if Mr. Uzui really is with Inosuke and the others right now, then I can rest easy.
Keep it down out there, will ya?
Is that a sword in your head, kid?
You've got a lot of nerve-picking fights out in front of my house.
What kind of mischief is this?
We made too much noise and now people are in danger.
I'll have you know that this Hanamachi is only viable because we and our clients all follow the rules.
So if you're gonna cause trouble, you're not welcome here.
Get the hell out of my sight!
You should keep your mouth shut.
This is bad.
Please, sir, don't come this way!
Huh?
Stay back, please!
It's too dangerous! Get back inside!
Get back inside!
Aro, please! Get up! We have to run! We have to run!
Stay calm.
Sir, you're going to survive this.
But your arm.
You need to stop the bleeding.
Aro, please!
Get up! We have to run! We have to run!
Stay calm.
Sir, you're going to survive this.
But your arm.
Get back here.
I won't let you get away with this!
Not after what you just did!
What's wrong?
You still have something to say?
Your efforts are useless and you're hideous.
There's no reason to let ugly people like yourself live.
So do us a favor and die alongside them.
Aro, wake up!
We have to leave!
Help us!
Somebody help us, please!
Everyone get back inside!
It's too dangerous to stay out here!
Dear Kamado, I know now that I wronged you.
Thank you for shedding the tears I couldn't over my son, Kyojuro.
And if I'm not mistaken, you've been exchanging letters with Senjuro for the past four months or so.
He seems to be in a much better place now.
I'm horribly ashamed that our first meeting went the way that it did.
At a time when my own incompetence had left me shattered, things went from bad to worse when my beloved wife succumbed to illness.
Since then, I've done nothing but drink myself into a stupor and wallow.
I've been a useless father.
Thankfully, Kyojuro somehow turned out to be a fine son.
Even after I abandoned him as an instructor and a father, he pushed forward studying the guide to flame breathing and became a Hashira.
Although there are only three volumes, he must have more of his mother, Luka's blood in him.
Both Kyojuro and Senjuro are fine boys.
But Kamado, you are just as exceptional, if not more, young man.
Rumor has it that those who are chosen to wield sun-breathing are born with the same red mark on their forehead that you have.
So I'm sure that you will.
No, you're wrong, Mr. Shinjiro.
I wasn't born with this scar to begin with.
Originally, it was just a burn mark from when I protected my younger brother from a falling brazier.
After that, I was injured during final selection, which is how it ended up the way it is now.
I was told that my father was born with a faint mark on his forehead, but that wasn't the case with me.
Which means I must not be one of the chosen wielders that you're talking about.
But that doesn't matter right now.
Even if I'm not one of the chosen ones, even if I'm not up to the task, there are times like this where I can't just back down.
Because in this world, there are those that lack any trace of a human heart.
Killing innocent people without any hesitation, and moving on without any regret.
She is that kind of evil, but as long as I live, I won't allow it!
Those lost lives will never return!
They can't just regenerate!
That's a luxury only demons have!
Why do you kill?
Why trample over the lives of the innocent?
I feel like I've heard these same words before.
Such disregard for human life. What's so amusing about this?
So tell me then, what is the weight of a human life to you?
Wait, who was that?
Why can't you understand?
How could you ever forget?
Something's not right.
I don't remember this.
These aren't my memories at all.
It must be the cells.
They're Lord Muzan's memories.
I saved everyone who was trapped in here, so what's the issue?
You should be on your knees worshipping me right now.
We'll talk about the other thing later.
Lord Tengen, if you don't go after it, there'll be even more bloodshed.
Don't worry about us and get over there before it's too late.
You heard what they said.
Get ready. We're giving chase.
Take out the base, boys.
Get out of my way, because Lord Tengen is coming through.
How the hell is he so fast?
What is it? Spit it out.
You were once a human. Isn't that right?
Which means you shed tears and suffered like any other normal human would.
Just when I thought you couldn't get any more annoying.
Luckily, I don't remember anything about the past.
I'm a demon now, so who cares about my human past?
Life is better like this.
Us demons don't have to buy food or grow old.
Or get sick or die.
We have nothing to lose.
Not to mention...
Beautiful, powerful demons can do anything we want!
Blood demon art!
Eight lair to obi-slash!
Let's see how an idiot like you stops an attack like this.
A crossblow leaving you with nowhere to run.
Using the parts of my body that were split off to take control of this area.
Now that I'm whole again, my speed is in a class of its own.
Seeing as you could barely hold your own against my non-blood demon art, it's all over for you.
So, hideous boy, I'm going to cut you and that decrepit sword into pieces.
Now then, I'll be making my way to that Hashira!
Hinokami Kagura, Burning Bones, Summer Sun.
This pain! What just happened?
It feels like I've just suffered burns where I received that slash!
Which means I can't regenerate!
But his wounds must be deep too!
Making such violent motions should have instantly ruptured everything within his body!
What? How is he able to slice my belt?
Something's not right here!
My fingertips are trembling?
This isn't like me!
Lord Muzan!
Damn it!
Why is he faster than before?
None of this makes any sense!
Don't you feel any pain?
Are you human?
As if someone like you could ever hope to decapitate a demon as strong as me!
It's soft.
Too soft for me to cut through.
It was able to blunt my slash by bending.
I won't let you get away!
You hideous!
Why are you dumb?
There are more belts now.
Thirteen of them.
If I dodge them, they might wreak even more havoc.
But for some reason...
They're moving so slowly.
Just try and cut me now!
You can't!
That last exchange of ours was nothing more than a fluke!
What?
He gathered all of my belts in one spot!
You think that's enough to stop me?
It'll take more than that!
You might be able to pull them tight enough to cut through.
But I can loosen them all again in the blink of an eye.
So unless you can close the distance between us faster than that, you...
What?
He slashed them!
He's fast!
It's simple, really.
I just had to bring my sword down faster than they could start bending.
I can decapitate her this time.
It's over.
Brother, please!
You have to breathe!
Hurry!
You humans never cease to amaze me with how pathetic you all are.
If that really was the best you could do, then I might actually be starting to feel a little bit bad for you.
I can't stop coughing.
It's so hard...
To breathe!
Which means I must have gone well beyond my stamina threshold.
My vision's going dark.
All I can hear is the sound of my heartbeat.
Since you're human, I'm afraid your wounds won't be healing anytime soon.
Blame your own flesh and blood.
Stand up.
Wield your sword.
But I'll do you a favor, and show you how to decapitate your enemy!
Hey!
You have some nerve doing that!
Wait a second. That filthy traitor. It's you, isn't it?
The one he was talking about has to be you!
Daki. There's a demon out there that managed to slip from my grasp.
Just as Tamayo did.
I need you to find and dispose of her.
You're the only one I can turn to.
It shouldn't be hard to recognize her.
She's a girl clad in a hemp-leaf-patterned kimono and a checkered belt.
Lord Muzan!
I will happily eviscerate this hideous little runt!
Prepare to die, scum!
Is chicken the only thing you know?!
You've got to beat her!
Could you be any weaker?
You've barely consumed any humans.
It's a miracle you were able to escape Lord Muzan.
Aw, you poor thing.
Your torso and lower body went their separate ways.
I wouldn't try moving if I were you.
After all, there's no way a half-developed demon like yourself could possibly regenerate quickly enough to continue fighting.
But since we're both demons, I'll quit toying around with you.
And instead, I'll absorb you into my belt and expose you to the sun in the morning.
Like I'd waste my time finishing you off when I have a Hashira to kill.
What's going on?
She's regenerated her leg.
Never mind her leg.
How is she able to stand?
I'm sure I severed her in half.
I saw it with my own eyes.
There's no way I missed!
I didn't expect this.
Her healing and regeneration speed is on par with upper-ranked demons.
What is this intimidating presence that's radiating from her?
Her whole demeanor's changed.
Brother...
You and Sister sure do take after one another.
You're gentle, but scary when you get mad.
Like Sister, when that scary grown-up bumped into a kid and hurt him, she got in his face, demanding he apologize.
I mean, luckily there were tons of adults around, but...
It still made me nervous.
People who get mad at others don't tend to have any regard for their own safety.
Because of that, they risk losing so much, which...
Well...
It scares me.
Another kick!
There goes two of your limbs!
Now for your neck!
Me.
Thright!
Words.
Thank you.
Can you see ahead of you?
Is this any better?
Whoa, that's pretty good for you.
Hey, where'd the Gata Festivals go?
You two better pick up the pace.
Gata Festivals!
We're out of time, so there's no Taisho era secret today.
Next, episode seven, transformation.
Now, quick, Coupida!
Let's go!